University of Connecticut 1998.0189
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series V:, 1987
  - University Files (Red Files)
    - Engineering: Accreditation (Box 22:, Folder 980)
      - National Center for Manufacturing Sciences Proposal (Box 22:, Folder 981)
      - Sematech (Box 22:, Folder 982)
      - UTC Building Dedication (Box 22:, Folder 983)
    - Engineering II: Equipment Furnishings (Box 22:, Folder 984)
    - English Department (Box 22:, Folder 985-986)
    - Enrollment (Box 22:, Folder 987-988)
    - Exchange Program
      - France (Box 22:, Folder 989)
      - Germany (Box 22:, Folder 990)
      - Netherlands (Box 22:, Folder 991)
      - Paraiba (Box 22:, Folder 992)
      - Poland (Box 22:, Folder 993)
      - Turkey (Box 22:, Folder 994)
    - Extended and Continuing Education (Box 22:, Folder 995)
    - External Affairs/University Relations: Vice President Search (Box 22:, Folder 996)
    - F (Box 22:, Folder 997)
    - Facilities (Box 22:, Folder 998-999)
    - Faculty Handbook (Box 22:, Folder 1000)
    - Faculty/Staff Development Center (Box 22:, Folder 1001)
    - Family Studies Development (Box 22:, Folder 1002)
    - Finance and Administration (Box 22:, Folder 1003)
    - Finance
      - Endowments, South Africa (Box 22:, Folder 1004)
      - Financial Aid (Box 22:, Folder 1005)
      - Vice President (Box 22:, Folder 1006)
      - Vice President Search (Box 22:, Folder 1007)
    - Fine Arts (Box 22:, Folder 1008-1010)
    - Founders Day (Box 22:, Folder 1011)
    - Framework for UConn Communication (Box 22:, Folder 1012)
    - Fraternities/Sororities (Box 22:, Folder 1013)
    - Gant, Ed and Margaret (Box 22:, Folder 1014)
    - Gehrung Associates (Box 22:, Folder 1015)
    - Geology (Box 22:, Folder 1016)
    - Government Relations (Box 22:, Folder 1017-1019)
    - Graduate School (Box 22:, Folder 1020)
    - Greek Orthodox Center (Box 22:, Folder 1021)
    - Handicapped Riding Program (Box 23:, Folder 1022)
    - Health Center (Box 23:, Folder 1023-1025)
      - Collective Bargaining (Box 23:, Folder 1026)
      - Endowed Chairs (Box 23:, Folder 1027)
      - Farm Hollow Lease (Box 23:, Folder 1028)
      - Iterations (Box 23:, Folder 1029)
      - John Dempsey Hospital (Box 23:, Folder 1030-1032)
      - Master Site plan Study (Box 23:, Folder 1033-1034)
      - Physical Health Services (Box 23:, Folder 1035)
      - Uncas on Thames (Box 23:, Folder 1036)
    - Hillel House (Box 23:, Folder 1037)
    - Historian, State (Box 23:, Folder 1038)
    - History (Box 23:, Folder 1039)
    - Housing: Mansfield/Northwood (Box 23:, Folder 1040)
    - Institute of Materials Science (Box 23:, Folder 1041)
    - Institute of Public Service (Box 23:, Folder 1042)
    - Institutional Relations (Box 23:, Folder 1043)
    - Institutional Relations: Davidoff (Box 23:, Folder 1044)
    - Institutional Research (Box 23:, Folder 1045-1046)
    - International Affairs: Associate Vice President Search (Box 23:, Folder 1047)
    - International Programs (Box 23:, Folder 1048)
    - Inventory (Box 23:, Folder 1049)
    - Islamic Center (Box 23:, Folder 1050)
    - Jewish Matters (Box 23:, Folder 1051)
    - Jewish Studies: Joint Sepphoris Excavations Project (Box 23:, Folder 1052)
    - Labor Relations (Box 23:, Folder 1053)
    - Latin Americans In Higher Education (Box 23:, Folder 1054)
    - Latin American Studies (Box 23:, Folder 1055)
    - Law School
      - Accreditation (Box 23:, Folder 1056)
      - Commencement (Box 23:, Folder 1057)
      - Foundation audit, 1987 (Box 23:, Folder 1058)
      - Gallivan Chair, 1984-1987 (Box 23:, Folder 1059)
      - Library (Box 23:, Folder 1060)
    - Legionnaires Disease (Box 23:, Folder 1061)
    - Liberal Arts and Sciences (Box 23:, Folder 1062)
    - Library (Box 23:, Folder 1063-1065)
    - M (Box 23:, Folder 1066)
    - Mansfield, Town of (Box 23:, Folder 1067)
    - Marine Sciences: Sea Grant (Box 23:, Folder 1068)
    - Marine Sciences Institute (Box 23:, Folder 1069)
    - Mathematics Department (Box 23:, Folder 1070)
    - Metanoia (Box 23:, Folder 1071)
    - Minorities (Box 23:, Folder 1072)
    - Minorities: CAP (Box 24:, Folder 1073)
      - Rankin Report (Box 24:, Folder 1074)
    - Moving Expenses (Box 24:, Folder 1075)
    - Music (Box 24:, Folder 1076-1077)
    - Museum, Benton (Box 24:, Folder 1078-1079)
    - Museum of Natural History (Box 24:, Folder 1080)
    - Near Death Studies (Box 24:, Folder 1081)
    - Northwood Apartments (Box 24:, Folder 1082)
    - Nursing (Box 24:, Folder 1083)
    - Ombudsman (Box 24:, Folder 1084)
    - PTR (Box 24:, Folder 1085)
    - Parking (Box 24:, Folder 1086-1088)
    - Part-Time Faculty Salary Structure Position Paper (Box 24:, Folder 1089)
    - Peace Education Group (Box 24:, Folder 1090)
    - Personnel (Box 24:, Folder 1091)
    - Pharmacy (Box 24:, Folder 1092-1093)
    - Philosophy (Box 24:, Folder 1094)
    - Photo Lab (Box 24:, Folder 1095)
    - Planning (Box 24:, Folder 1096)
    - Police Department (Box 24:, Folder 1097)
    - Political Science (Box 24:, Folder 1098)
    - Positions (PC) (Box 24:, Folder 1099)
    - President
      - Address to Faculty (Box 24:, Folder 1100-1101)
      - Auto (Box 24:, Folder 1102)
      - Driver (Box 24:, Folder 1103)
      - Residence (Box 24:, Folder 1104)
      - Retreat (Box 24:, Folder 1105-1106)
    - Provost Search (Box 24:, Folder 1107)
    - Publications (Box 24:, Folder 1108)
    - Purchasing (Box 24:, Folder 1109)
    - Regional Campuses
      - Hartford (Box 24:, Folder 1110)
      - Southeastern (Box 24:, Folder 1111-1113)
      - Stamford (Box 24:, Folder 1114-1115)
      - Torrington (Box 24:, Folder 1116)
      - Waterbury (Box 24:, Folder 1117)
    - Regional Campus: Fall visits (Box 24:, Folder 1118-1122)
    - Registrar (Box 24:, Folder 1123)
    - Reorganization (Box 24:, Folder 1124)
    - Research Consultants: John Lee (Box 24:, Folder 1125)
    - Research Foundation (Box 24:, Folder 1126)
    - Research and Development Corporation (Box 24:, Folder 1127)
    - Retirement, mandatory (Box 24:, Folder 1128)
    - ROTC (Box 24:, Folder 1129-1130)
    - Sabbatic Leaves (Box 24:, Folder 1131)
    - Salaries (Box 24:, Folder 1132-1134)
    - Scholarships (Box 25:, Folder 1135-1137)
    - Senate (Box 25:, Folder 1138)
    - Signature Authority (Box 25:, Folder 1139)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 25:, Folder 1140-1141)
    - South Africa (Box 25:, Folder 1142)
    - Space Allocation (Box 25:, Folder 1143-1145)
    - Special Olympics (Box 25:, Folder 1146)
    - Spirer/Robinson Award (Box 25:, Folder 1147)
    - Student Affairs
      - Associated Student Commissaries (Box 25:, Folder 1148)
      - Career Services (Box 25:, Folder 1149)
      - Day of Pride (Box 25:, Folder 1150)
      - Disciplinary Actions, Landolfi/Doyle (Box 25:, Folder 1151)
      - Food Services (Box 25:, Folder 1152)
      - Goals (Box 25:, Folder 1153)
      - Health Services (Box 25:, Folder 1154)
      - Orientation (Box 25:, Folder 1155)
      - Residential Life (Box 25:, Folder 1156-1159)
      - Student Life Committee (Box 25:, Folder 1160)
      - Special Populations Report (Box 25:, Folder 1161)
    - Student Organizations
      - Daily Campus (Box 25:, Folder 1162)
      - Intra-Fraternity Council (Box 25:, Folder 1163)
      - Undergraduate Student Government (Box 25:, Folder 1164)
      - Student Union Board of Governors (Box 25:, Folder 1165)
    - TAFS (Box 25:, Folder 1166)
    - Task Labor (Box 25:, Folder 1167)
    - Technology Center (Box 25:, Folder 1168)
    - Telecommunications (Box 25:, Folder 1169)
    - Tenure (Box 25:, Folder 1170)
    - Transportation (Box 25:, Folder 1171)
    - Tuition Dues (Box 25:, Folder 1172)
    - UCEPI (Box 25:, Folder 1173-1176)
    - UConn Foundation (Box 25:, Folder 1177-1180)
    - University Press of New England (Box 25:, Folder 1181)
    - University Professor (Box 25:, Folder 1182)
    - University Relations/External Affairs: Vice President Search (Box 25:, Folder 1183)
    - V (Box 25:, Folder 1184)
    - Water Line, Hunting Lodge Road (Box 25:, Folder 1185)
    - Water Resources Institute (Box 25:, Folder 1186)
    - Women's Center (Box 25:, Folder 1187)
    - Women's Studies (Box 25:, Folder 1188)
  - State Government (Blue Files)
    - Agriculture (Box 26:, Folder 1189)
    - Appropriations Committee (Box 26:, Folder 1190)
    - Attorney General (Box 26:, Folder 1191)
    - Auditor
      - Associated Student Government (Box 26:, Folder 1192)
      - Creamery (Box 26:, Folder 1193)
      - Fiscal Year ending June 30, 1986 and 1987 (Box 26:, Folder 1194)
      - Health Center, Computer Components Theft (Box 26:, Folder 1195)
      - Health Center, Fiscal Years 1984, 1985, 1986 (Box 26:, Folder 1196)
      - Health Center, Purchasing Violations (Box 26:, Folder 1197)
      - Plant Science (Box 26:, Folder 1198)
      - Report, Fiscal Year Ended June 30, 1984 and 1985 (Box 26:, Folder 1199)
      - Special Local Fund (Box 26:, Folder 1200)
      - Undergraduate Student Government, 1985-86 (Box 26:, Folder 1201)
      - Waterbury Associated Student Government, 1985-86 (Box 26:, Folder 1202)
    - Board of Governors (Box 26:, Folder 1203)
    - Bonding Subcommittee (Box 26:, Folder 1204)
    - Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 26:, Folder 1205)
      - Plan (Box 26:, Folder 1206)
    - Common Core of Learning (Box 26:, Folder 1207)
    - Comptroller (Box 26:, Folder 1208)
    - Connecticut Council on Higher Education (Box 26:, Folder 1209)
    - Cooperative Extension Legislature Task Force (Box 26:, Folder 1210)
    - Department of Administrative Services (Box 26:, Folder 1211-1212)
    - Department of Education (Box 26:, Folder 1213)
    - DHE
      - December (Box 26:, Folder 1214)
      - November (Box 26:, Folder 1215)
      - October (Box 26:, Folder 1216)
      - September (Box 26:, Folder 1217)
      - August (Box 26:, Folder 1218)
      - July (Box 26:, Folder 1219)
      - June (Box 26:, Folder 1220)
      - May (Box 26:, Folder 1221)
      - April (Box 26:, Folder 1222-1223)
      - March (Box 26:, Folder 1224)
      - February (Box 26:, Folder 1225)
      - January (Box 26:, Folder 1226)
      - Center for Excellence (Box 27:, Folder 1227-1228)
      - Conncap (Box 27:, Folder 1229)
      - Educational Cost Equity (Box 27:, Folder 1230)
      - Fairfield County Study (Box 27:, Folder 1231)
      - Formula Budgeting (Box 27:, Folder 1232)
      - Independent Colleges, Contracting with (Box 27:, Folder 1233)
      - Legislative Agenda (Box 27:, Folder 1234)
      - Minority Retention Recruitment (Box 27:, Folder 1235)
      - Minority Staff Advancement (Box 27:, Folder 1236)
      - Mission Statements (Box 27:, Folder 1237)
      - Off-Campus Offerings (Box 27:, Folder 1238)
    - Economic Development (Box 27:, Folder 1239)
    - Environmental Protection (Box 27:, Folder 1240)
    - Ethics Commission (Box 27:, Folder 1241)
    - F (Box 27:, Folder 1242)
    - Finance Revenue and Bonding Subcommittee (Box 27:, Folder 1243)
    - General Assembly (Box 27:, Folder 1244)
    - Governor: Mt. Auburn Association (Box 27:, Folder 1245)
    - Governor's Office, 1986-1987 (Box 27:, Folder 1246)
    - Governor's Task Force on Student Financial Aid (Box 27:, Folder 1247)
    - Governor's Technology Advisory Board, 1986-1987 (Box 27:, Folder 1248)
    - Legislative Internships (Box 27:, Folder 1249)
    - Legislative Thank Yous (Box 27:, Folder 1250)
    - Legislators
      - Senator Ends (Box 27:, Folder 1251)
      - Representative Fleming (Box 27:, Folder 1252)
      - Senator Herbst (Box 27:, Folder 1253)
      - Representative Kiner (Box 27:, Folder 1254)
      - Senator McLaughlin (Box 27:, Folder 1255)
      - Representative Pelto (Box 27:, Folder 1256)
      - Representative Przybysz (Box 27:, Folder 1257)
      - Representative Saxon-Perry (Box 27:, Folder 1258)
      - Representative Stolberg (Box 27:, Folder 1259)
      - Senator Sullivan (Box 27:, Folder 1260)
      - Senator Upson (Box 27:, Folder 1261)
      - Representative Woodcock (Box 27:, Folder 1262)
    - Litchfield County Higher Education Center (Box 27:, Folder 1263)
    - Manchester Community College (Box 27:, Folder 1264)
    - Minority Caucus (Box 27:, Folder 1265)
    - Office of Policy and Management (Box 27:, Folder 1266)
    - Personnel (Box 27:, Folder 1267)
    - Public Works (Box 27:, Folder 1268)
    - Purchases Bureau (Box 27:, Folder 1269)
    - Properties Review Board (Box 27:, Folder 1270)
    - Transportation (Box 27:, Folder 1271)
  - Federal Government (Green Files)
    - AFL-CIO (Box 27:, Folder 1272)
    - Agriculture (Box 27:, Folder 1273)
    - Air Force (Box 27:, Folder 1274)
    - Budget (Box 27:, Folder 1275)
    - Congressional Inquiries
      - Chris Dodd, 1985-1987 (Box 27:, Folder 1276)
      - Sam Gejdenson (Box 27:, Folder 1277)
      - Scott Jackson (Box 27:, Folder 1278)
      - John Rowland (Box 27:, Folder 1279)
      - Christopher Shays (Box 27:, Folder 1280)
      - Lowell Weicker (Box 27:, Folder 1281)
    - Constitution Bicentennial (Box 27:, Folder 1282)
    - Dempsey, John, 1985-1989 (Box 27:, Folder 1283)
    - E, 1986-1987 (Box 27:, Folder 1284)
    - Education (Box 27:, Folder 1285)
    - Environmental Protection (Box 27:, Folder 1286)
    - Equal Employment Opportunities Commission (Box 27:, Folder 1287)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 27:, Folder 1288)
    - G, 1986-1987 (Box 27:, Folder 1289)
    - General Accounting Office (Box 27:, Folder 1290)
    - Handicapped Access Section 504 (Box 27:, Folder 1291)
    - Labor Office of Federal Contract Compliance (Box 27:, Folder 1292)
    - Navy (Box 27:, Folder 1293)
    - NASA (Box 27:, Folder 1294)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 27:, Folder 1295)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission (Box 27:, Folder 1296)
    - Savings Bonds (Box 27:, Folder 1297)
    - VISTA (Box 27:, Folder 1298)
  - Organizations (Black Files)
    - Association of American Publishers, Inc. (Box 28:, Folder 1299)
    - Hartford Courant (Box 28:, Folder 1300)
    - Hartford Graduate Center (Box 28:, Folder 1301)
    - Kraig, Bonnie (Box 28:, Folder 1302)
    - Kraus, Harold (Box 28:, Folder 1303)
    - Marland, S.P. (Box 28:, Folder 1304)
    - Otis Elevator Company (Box 28:, Folder 1305)
    - P (Box 28:, Folder 1306)
    - Questionnaires (Box 28:, Folder 1307)
    - Research Corporation (Box 28:, Folder 1308)
    - S (Box 28:, Folder 1309)
    - Tolland Foundation (Box 28:, Folder 1310)
    - United Way, 1986-1987 (Box 28:, Folder 1311)
    - University of Hartford, 1986-1987 (Box 28:, Folder 1312)
  - Education Associations (Yellow Files)
    - ACE, 1987-1988 (Box 28:, Folder 1313)
    - American Council of Education (Box 28:, Folder 1314)
    - Association of Urban Universities (Box 28:, Folder 1315)
    - Campus Compact (Box 28:, Folder 1316)
    - College Entrance Examination Board (Box 28:, Folder 1317)
    - Consortium of Social Sciences Association (Box 28:, Folder 1318)
    - Council of Presidents (Box 28:, Folder 1319-1323)
    - Education Commission of the States (Box 28:, Folder 1324)
    - Financial Aid (Box 28:, Folder 1325)
    - NASULGC (Box 28:, Folder 1326-1328)
    - National Consortium for Educational Associations (Box 28:, Folder 1329)
    - NEBHE (Box 28:, Folder 1330-1332)
    - New England Association of Schools and Colleges (Box 28:, Folder 1333-1334)
- Series VI:, 1988
  - University Files (Red Files)
    - Academic Action (Box 29:, Folder 1335)
    - Administration: Property Considerations (Box 29:, Folder 1336)
    - Administration: Vice President (Box 29:, Folder 1337)
    - Admissions (Box 29:, Folder 1338-1340)
    - Affirmative Action (Box 29:, Folder 1341-1343)
    - Affirmative Action: Advisory Committee (Box 29:, Folder 1344)
    - Aging, Travelers Center on (Box 29:, Folder 1345)
    - Agriculture and Natural Resources (Box 29:, Folder 1346)
    - Agriculture: Dairy Bar/Creamery (Box 29:, Folder 1347)
    - Agriculture: Holcomb/Granby Property (Box 29:, Folder 1348)
    - AIDS (Box 29:, Folder 1349)
    - Alcohol/Drugs (Box 29:, Folder 1350)
    - Allied Health (Box 29:, Folder 1351-1352)
    - Alumni
      - Insurance (Box 29:, Folder 1353)
      - Margin for Excellence (Box 29:, Folder 1354)
    - Alumni Association (Box 29:, Folder 1355-1357)
    - Alumni House (Box 29:, Folder 1358)
    - Animal Care (Box 29:, Folder 1359)
    - Appointment Letter Problems (Box 29:, Folder 1360)
    - Arboretum, Bartlett (Box 29:, Folder 1361)
    - Archeologist (Box 29:, Folder 1362)
    - Architecture, School of (Box 29:, Folder 1363)
    - Archives Building (Box 29:, Folder 1364)
    - Assistant to the President: Ann Huckenbeck (Box 29:, Folder 1365)
    - Athletics (Box 29:, Folder 1366-1367)
      - Basketball (Box 29:, Folder 1368)
      - Drug Testing (Box 29:, Folder 1369)
      - Multi-Purpose Field House (Gampel) Progress Report (Box 29:, Folder 1370)
      - NCAA (Box 29:, Folder 1371-1372)
      - NCAA Faculty Representative (Box 29:, Folder 1373)
      - Ski Team Funding (Box 29:, Folder 1374)
      - Sports Center (Box 29:, Folder 1375)
      - Ticket Priority Seating Locations (Box 29:, Folder 1376)
      - UConn Club (Box 29:, Folder 1377)
      - Yankee Conference (Box 29:, Folder 1378)
    - Attorney (Box 29:, Folder 1379)
    - Audit Subcommittee (Box 29:, Folder 1380)
    - Auditor
      - Accounts Receivable, Regional Campus (Box 29:, Folder 1381)
      - Activity Report (Box 29:, Folder 1382)
      - Associated Student Government (Box 29:, Folder 1383)
      - MBA Fee Recoveries (Box 29:, Folder 1384)
      - Non-Audit Functions (Box 29:, Folder 1385)
      - Office of Facilities - Modular Office Space (Box 29:, Folder 1386)
    - Auditorium (Box 29:, Folder 1387)
    - Barney House (Box 30:, Folder 1388)
    - Behavioral Science (Box 30:, Folder 1389)
    - Biotechnology (Box 30:, Folder 1390)
    - Bomb Threats (Box 30:, Folder 1391)
    - Budget
      - 1988-1989: January - June (Box 30:, Folder 1392-1393)
      - 1989-1990: January - June, 1988 (Box 30:, Folder 1394-1395)
      - 1989-1990: July - December, 1988 (Box 30:, Folder 1396)
      - 1989-1990: July, 1988 (Box 30:, Folder 1397-1399)
      - 1989-1990: August, 1988 (Box 30:, Folder 1400-1401)
      - 1989-1990: September, 1988 (Box 30:, Folder 1402-1404)
      - Capital Budget Issues (Box 30:, Folder 1405)
      - DHE Capital Budget Hearing (Box 30:, Folder 1406)
      - Five-Year Equipment Facilities Plan (Box 30:, Folder 1407)
      - Rental Property Reserves (Box 30:, Folder 1408)
      - Reserves (Box 30:, Folder 1409)
      - Temporary Labor (Box 30:, Folder 1410)
    - Bursar (Box 30:, Folder 1411)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 30:, Folder 1412-1413)
    - Center, Small Business Development (Box 30:, Folder 1414)
    - Center for Instructional Media (Box 30:, Folder 1415)
    - Center for Real Estate (Box 30:, Folder 1416)
    - Child Development Lab (Box 30:, Folder 1417)
    - Collective Bargaining
      - AAUP (Box 30:, Folder 1418)
      - Flex Time (Box 30:, Folder 1419)
      - Health Center (Box 30:, Folder 1420)
      - Independent (Box 30:, Folder 1421)
      - UCPEA (Box 30:, Folder 1422-1424)
    - Committees (Box 30:, Folder 1425)
    - Communication Science (Box 30:, Folder 1426)
    - Computer Center (Box 30:, Folder 1427)
    - ConnTech (Box 30:, Folder 1428)
    - Convocation (Box 30:, Folder 1429)
    - Core Curriculum (Box 30:, Folder 1430)
    - Dental Medicine (Box 31:, Folder 1431)
    - Development (Box 31:, Folder 1432-1433)
      - A - H (Box 31:, Folder 1434)
      - K - M (Box 31:, Folder 1435)
      - P - Z (Box 31:, Folder 1436)
      - Aetna (Box 31:, Folder 1437)
      - Annual Fund (Box 31:, Folder 1438)
      - Corporate Roundtable (Box 31:, Folder 1439)
      - Dinners (Box 31:, Folder 1440)
      - General Electric (Box 31:, Folder 1441)
      - Howard Hughes Foundation (Box 31:, Folder 1442)
      - IBM (Box 31:, Folder 1443-1445)
      - Israel Bonds (Box 31:, Folder 1446)
      - Jewish Prospects (Box 31:, Folder 1447)
      - Klebanoff (Box 31:, Folder 1448)
      - Kresge (Box 31:, Folder 1449)
      - Noether (Box 31:, Folder 1450)
      - Roger Tory Peterson (Box 31:, Folder 1451)
      - Israel and Joyce Resnikoff (Box 31:, Folder 1452)
      - Sigmund Strochlitz (Box 31:, Folder 1453)
      - Wolff - Zackin (Box 31:, Folder 1454)
    - Economics Department (Box 31:, Folder 1455)
    - Education, School of (Box 31:, Folder 1456)
    - Education: Mullarney/Indelicato (Box 31:, Folder 1457)
    - Educational Innovation, Center for (Box 31:, Folder 1458)
    - Emergency Preparedness (Box 31:, Folder 1459)
    - Emeriti (Box 31:, Folder 1460)
    - Employee Recognition (Box 31:, Folder 1461)
    - Endowed Chairs (Box 31:, Folder 1462)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 31:, Folder 1463-1465)
    - English (Box 31:, Folder 1466)
    - Enrollment (Box 31:, Folder 1467)
    - Environmental Health and Safety (Box 31:, Folder 1468)
    - Exchange Programs (Box 31:, Folder 1469)
    - Exchange Programs (Box 31:, Folder 1470-1471)
    - Extended and Continuing Education (Box 31:, Folder 1472)
    - Facilities (Box 31:, Folder 1473)
    - Family Studies (Box 31:, Folder 1474-1475)
    - Finance: Financial Aid (Box 31:, Folder 1476)
    - Finance: Vice President Jones (Box 31:, Folder 1477-1478)
    - Fine Arts (Box 32:, Folder 1479)
    - Fraternities/Sororities (Box 32:, Folder 1480)
    - Government Relations (Box 32:, Folder 1481-1482)
    - Graduate School (Box 32:, Folder 1483)
    - Grants and Contracts (Box 32:, Folder 1484)
    - Greek Chapel and Cultural Center (Box 32:, Folder 1485)
    - Harassment (Box 32:, Folder 1486)
    - Hartford Steam Boiler (Box 32:, Folder 1487)
    - Health Center
      - January - June (Box 32:, Folder 1488-1489)
      - July - December (Box 32:, Folder 1490-1492)
      - Farm Hollow Lease (Box 32:, Folder 1493)
      - Hospital Support Building (Box 32:, Folder 1494)
      - John Dempsey Hospital (Box 32:, Folder 1495)
      - Mount Sinai (Box 32:, Folder 1496)
      - Newington Children's Hospital (Box 32:, Folder 1497)
      - Parking (Box 32:, Folder 1498)
      - Physician and Dentist Audit (Box 32:, Folder 1499)
      - Physician Health Services (Box 32:, Folder 1500)
      - Helen Smits Salary Tenure (Box 32:, Folder 1501-1503)
      - Uncas on the Thames (Box 32:, Folder 1504)
    - Historian, State (Box 32:, Folder 1505)
    - History Department (Box 32:, Folder 1506)
    - Honors Program (Box 32:, Folder 1507)
    - Housing (Box 32:, Folder 1508)
    - Hunting Lodge: Water Line (Box 32:, Folder 1509)
    - Institute of Materials Science (Box 32:, Folder 1510)
    - Institute of Public Relations (Box 32:, Folder 1511)
    - Institutional Relations (Box 32:, Folder 1512-1513)
    - Institutional Research (Box 32:, Folder 1514)
    - Institutional Programs (Box 32:, Folder 1515)
    - Jewish Matters (Box 32:, Folder 1516)
    - Job Sharing (Box 32:, Folder 1517)
    - Judaic Studies (Box 32:, Folder 1518)
    - Labor Relations (Box 32:, Folder 1519)
    - Latin American Studies (Box 32:, Folder 1520)
    - Law School (Box 32:, Folder 1521-1522)
      - Commencement (Box 32:, Folder 1523)
      - Foundation (Box 32:, Folder 1524)
      - Insurance Center (Box 32:, Folder 1525)
      - Library (Box 32:, Folder 1526)
      - Renovations (Box 32:, Folder 1527)
    - Layoff Procedures (Box 32:, Folder 1528)
    - Liberal Arts (Box 33:, Folder 1529-1530)
    - Library
      - Security Issue (Box 33:, Folder 1531)
      - Structural Concerns (Box 33:, Folder 1532)
    - Mansfield, Town of (Box 33:, Folder 1533)
    - Marine Sciences: Research Vessel, Replacement Vessel (Box 33:, Folder 1534)
    - Marine Sciences: Sea Grant (Box 33:, Folder 1535)
    - Math Department (Box 33:, Folder 1536)